seekingmarriage.com 2008-11-21

# AzoogleAds Privacy Policy

Effective Date: March 10, 2005

Privacy Policy

Seeking Marriage (“Seeking Marriage”, “us” or “we”), has created this privacy policy (hereinafter the “Privacy Policy”) in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy and have designed our service with this in mind. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: 1) access or use  Seeking Marriage  (the “Website”); and/or 2) select and register for an offer(s) on the Website by clicking the offer(s) presented. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Website.

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for direct marketing purposes, please e-mail us at help@azoogleads.com. 

The information that we collect is generally limited to personal information about you that you submit on the Website. The personally identifiable information that may be collected includes: your name; address; email address; telephone number; fax number; information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services; and education level and interests. Although we are not collecting credit card information at this time, we reserve the right to do so in the future. To the extent that customer credit card-specific information is collected by  Seeking Marriage  and any of its affiliates and/or subsidiaries, said information will be kept in confidence and will not be shared with any third parties (other than consumer credit agencies) without the customer's prior informed consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing,  Seeking Marriage  and its affiliates and subsidiaries reserve the right to share with third parties the fact that they have credit card information on file for specific customers but they will not share this credit card information with third parties without the customer's prior informed consent.

Like most standard website servers, we use log files. Log files track anonymous user information including, but not limited to, Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (“ISP”), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information is tracked in order to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users' movements in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The information tracked via log files is not linked to personally identifiable information.

The Website uses a “cookie” to assign a unique identifier to your computer. The cookies we use are persistent files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies may be used to help save information on past activities and other preferences, so that you are not required to reenter information each time that you visit the Website, and to deliver content specific to your interests. No personally identifiable information is gathered by the cookie.

Any personal information that you supply to us remains your personal property. However, by submitting that information to Seeking Marriage , you grant us the right to use your personal information for any legal purpose including, without limitation: a) providing promotional offers to you via email advertising and/or online banner advertising; b) transferring the personal information that you provided to a third party, when necessary, to receive a product, service, or information that you may have requested from such third party while using the Website; c) tracking compliance with our Terms and Conditions; and d) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes.

By submitting your information to the Website, you grant Seeking Marriage the right to use that information for marketing purposes, and agree to receive email marketing from the Website. We may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. In order to end your email subscription to a particular list, you must follow the instructions contained in any email correspondence that you receive from Seeking Marriage . Unsubscribing from one list will not automatically unsubscribe you from all email lists. We only send email marketing to individuals that have agreed, whether by visiting this Website or through third party websites, to receive email marketing from Seeking Marriage . We do not send unsolicited bulk email. As a result, certain statutes, requiring particular formatting for unsolicited bulk email may not be applicable to the bulk email that is sent by Seeking Marriage .

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may be required to disclose personal information in some instances, such as: 1) when required by law wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or subpoena; 2) in the event that Seeking Marriage is sold or acquired; or 3) in the event that we believe that the Website is being, or has been, used in violation of our terms and conditions or to commit unlawful acts. Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when Seeking Marriage , in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your email address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the provisions of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time-to-time.

Seeking Marriage provides you with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from other third-party companies. To receive such offers, products and/or services your personally identifiable information supplied to us during the registration process will be shared with such third-party companies so that they may provide the product or service to you that you have ordered from them without requiring that you first complete another registration form.

By submitting your e-mail address at the Website you agree to receive e-mail marketing from Seeking Marriage and our third-party advertisers. We may sell our user information and/or join together with other businesses to bring selected opportunities to our users. We are able to offer third party services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be reached by our third-party advertisers. In addition, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 C.F.R. 310, et seq. (the “ATSR”). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, Seeking Marriage retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the Website, such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR and you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the ATSR.

Seeking Marriage is not responsible for any content, terms and conditions, or the privacy policies of any third party advertisers' websites. The entities that advertise and/or place banner ads at the Website including, but not limited to, third party advertisers, are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Seeking Marriage .

Visitors under 18 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at the Website. Seeking Marriage does not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of 18. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Furthermore, access to this information is strictly limited, and the information is not accessible to the public. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all Seeking Marriage user information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we use appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data.

In addition, Seeking Marriage has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. 

Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable technological precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

To stop receiving future communications from Seeking Marriage , please send an e-mail to help@azoogleads.com. To unsubscribe from a third party service, you must contact that third party directly.

Seeking Marriage reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice at the Website that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, we will notify users by posting the changes on this Website. Any and all changes to our Privacy Policy are effective immediately upon posting. The user's continued use of the Website and/or continued receipt of Seeking Marriage e-mails constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by the user to the terms of the modified Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices Seeking Marriage please feel free to contact us at pp_email@azoogleads.com, or in writing at AzoogleAds, 140 Allstate Parkway, Suite 505, Markham, ON, L3R 5Y8.
